To make the preferences appear on the phone, we
need to modify settings activity. In the on-create method
we're going to replace this to do with some code.
We're going to call addPreferencesFromResource with the pref_general xml
that we defined. Then we need to bind the
preference summary to the value of the location preference.
This means that when the user changes the preference,
the summary value underneath the label will be updated.
If you look at the declaration of this method,
we see that for a given preference, it sets a
preference change listener on it. If you scroll to
the top, you see that the settings activity actually implements
the interface on preference change listener. That method is
found down below, where we override the on preference change
method. Remember that our location preference is actually an
edit text preference. So, it won't fall into this case,
but it will fall in this case down here. Then,
in the settings UI you can see that the summary
is now this value. Make these changes in your app.
See the instructor notes for the lines of code you need.